(Howard:)Where, as I'm sure you know,
no one can hear you scream.
(Raj:)So, what do you gals do?
(Bethany:)I work at the Gap.
(Howard:)Really? How about that?
I've been to the Gap.
(Raj:)I've been there as well.
I like your T-shirts with the little pocket.
(Sarah:)I work there too.
(Second girl:)Not that anyone cares.
(Sarah:)You know, this place is boring.
(Bethany:)Yeah. Why don't we go somewhere else
and have some fun?
-[GIGGLING] Okay.
-Sure. We like fun.
(Howard:)We are fun people.
Uh, dark and fun.
(Bethany:)Come on. I know a place you'll really dig.
[HOWARD GASPS]
(Howard:)-Did you bring the black condoms?
-In my fanny pack.
(Howard:)Let's go.
[NEEDLE BUZZING]
(Raj:)Are you happy now?
(Howard:)Not particularly.